LUCAS DRAICHI

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

PROFILE

Experienced engineer with over 7 years of successful experience mainly in web development. Eager to contribute to team success through hard work, attention to detail and excellent organizational skills. Active participant in the cryptocurrency community.

CONTACT

+55 11 98793 8453

🔽 lucasdraichi@gmail.com

São Paulo, Brazil

EXPERIENCE

Sabido, Lead Front-end Engineer MAR 2020 - PRESENT

Micro-learning social network focused or perfect user experience.

Talentify, Lead Front-end Engineer FEV 2019 - MAR 2020

Creation and development of state-of-the-art dashboard.

2Mundos, Backend Developer JUL 2017 - OUT 2018

Fast pace development of several projects and close contact with customers.

IBM Brazil, Web Builder APR 2014 - SEP 2015

Development of landing pages, promotional pages for new products and the blog theme

SKILLS

JavaScript

Cypress

SCSS

Typescript

Python

Solidity

• • • • • •

EDUCATION

University Paulista UNIP
JAN 2012 - DEC 2015
Bachelor of Engineering in Computer
Engineering

HOBBIES

Code | Cryptocurrencies | Yoga | Kickboxing